[theme music playing]
[laughs]
[Helena] Each and every one of you
has a reason to betray me.
[Emilia] Eeny, meeny, miny, moe.
Moe, moe!
[Diego] Red Dragon didn't kill Mercedes.
Someone else was there.
That person killed Mercedes.
[Julio] Who else knows that you're back?
It's just Mom and Grandma.
They'll never suspect they've
let a wolf into their midst.
[Camia] They found the corpse
of one of Red Dragon's people,
and they can't identify whose body it is.
[Emilia] Don't feel bad. It's her fault.
She's a traitor.
[Lily] I tried to convince her
to join my side,
but she refused and chose
to side with the demon.
[Jaguar] Red Dragon didn't
come back to kill Mercedes,
or to have the Big Four's
deaths investigated.
There will be an important transaction.
[Diego] This could be our last chance
to take down Red Dragon.
She has a huge transaction coming up.
We have to catch her.
[Lily] That's why we can't fail.
-Lily.
-Arnaldo.
[Arnaldo] You haven't changed, Lily.
You still smell so good
even though you're rotten to the core.
Hey, Jepoy.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to get the firearms I bought.
I've already paid in full.
I really need them now.
-Where are they?
-Yes, I know that.
But I already gave them
to your friend last night.
Wait, what? Which friend
are you talking about?
Remember who introduced me to you?
It was Natalie.
Natalie?
Yes.
[tense music playing]
Okay, bro. Sorry for the trouble.
I'll just call Natalie.
All right, bro. Drive safely.
Give her my regards, okay?
[tense music continues]
[line rings]
[phone ringing]
[phone continues ringing]
Madrigal.
[sensual music playing]
Hello, lover.
Where are my weapons?
I have it. So come and get it.
I need them now, so give them back.
Why did you take them?
Um…
Because I was lonely,
and I want it to compensate…
…for my loneliness.
And I miss you a lot, Madrigal.
You know, you're really nuts.
I need those weapons, Natalie.
I paid for them, so give them back to me.
Well…
If you want it, come and get it.
[laughs]
You know what, Natalie?
Since you took them,
I think it's better
if you bring them back.
Oh, I love it when you get mad.
Well, if you want it, then I'll be there.
Bye, lover boy.
[sensual music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
According to our insider,
Red Dragon's transaction
will take place tonight.
So, prepare everything
for tonight's operation, okay?
Dismissed.
-Yes, sir.
Agent Salonga,
Red Dragon will be
transporting innocent civilians.
So please be careful.
Most of them are minors,
and they're being smuggled
to different parts of the world.
We'll make sure to save all of them.
Including your insider friend.
Give this to your friend.
It's a wiretapping device.
That way, we can record and listen in
on Red Dragon's transaction.
Then, once we've collected
enough evidence,
we'll break in and arrest her.
[suspenseful music playing]
Hurry and get them out of here.
Come on, move it!
Faster!
Hurry up!
-Madam.
-[Emilia] Make sure…
With all due respect…
I know how important
this transaction is to you.
Yes. My reputation is at stake.
That is why I don't think Emilia
should be in charge of this.
She's too inexperienced.
Are you questioning my decision?
Ah… No, Madam.
Emilia will eventually lead our group,
so I want you to respect her
the way you respect me.
Do you understand?
Yes, Madam.
My apologies.
[tense music playing]
[door opens]
[Jaguar's lackey] Boss,
Romulo's looking for you.
Jeez, I'm on my way, okay?
Hey, Boss.
Are you still there?
[coughs]
Ah… I'm sick.
Just take charge while I'm gone.
But, Boss, what are we supposed to do?
What are you? Newbies?
You guys know how this goes.
But, Boss…
You can handle it.
[coughs]
Anyway, I'm hanging up.
My throat's sore,
and I need to take a pill.
Get down from there, Mariano.
It's still uneven, let me do it.
But you might fall, ma'am.
I won't. This isn't my first time.
Now, get down from there.
See? It's just not even.
-But ma'am, it's dangerous.
-I'm fine.
-Camia.
-I can handle it. What?
Careful.
On a step ladder? I'll be fine, Damian.
[Damian] Hey.
There.
-Nice.
-There, all done.
Mariano, please turn
these Christmas lights on
-so we can see how it looks.
-Help me out, Dang.
-See, Damian? It's easy.
-Careful.
Oh!
[romantic music playing]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Looks like this isn't stable enough.
-They're beautiful.
-Right?
Yes, sir.
[romantic music playing]
[clears throat]
Diego, you have to wear
this wiretapping device at all times
so we can listen in on your conversations
with Red Dragon.
We'll only attack after
you give us the go signal.
Also, if something doesn't go as planned,
we'll be there right away.
We can't afford to fail, Lily.
We have to catch Red Dragon in the act.
You have to be careful, Diego.
Your safety is more important.
Lily, I trusted you before.
So, this time, can you trust me too?
Nothing bad is gonna happen to me.
You won't lose me.
I do trust you. But, please,
let me protect you.
I just want to make sure you're safe.
I know.
Stay safe, Diego.
This will be the last time
we'll ever be apart.
After this, you're finally
coming back to me.
[tense music playing]
Okay. Take care.
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" instrumental playing]
[Diego] All your battles
are my battles, Lily.
We've been partners since we were kids.
I know how brave you are,
but I'll still do whatever
I can to protect you.
Don't go back there anymore.
Don't worry, Lily.
Nothing bad is gonna happen to me.
I'll do everything I can in this mission
so we can be together again.
And after tonight,
I won't waste a moment.
I'll show you just how much I love you.
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" instrumental playing]
You've always been by
my side since the start, Diego.
You were always there
to help me in all my battles.
You're ready to risk your own life for me.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
Stop this wedding!
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" instrumental playing]
So, this time…
I'm going to make it up to you.
This time, I'll make sure
you'll be able to escape
Red Dragon's syndicate.
I won't let anything
bad happen to you, Diego.
[ominous music playing]
Mama, everything is ready. We can go now.
Oh! That is okay, baby girl.
I'll take it from here.
Am I not working hard enough, Mama?
[scoffs] No, you're doing great.
It's just that the buyer
wants to meet me personally.
So, why don't you just stay here
and hold the fort while I'm gone?
Baby girl, I'm so proud of you.
Thank you, Mama.
[ominous music playing]
[suspenseful music swells]
Remember, we'll wait for the go
signal of Lily Cruz's contact.
-Yes, sir.
[tense music playing]
[soft piano music playing]
Oh!
[soft piano music continues]
Hey! My bag!
-Call the cops!
-Officer!
Here's your bag. It's good as new, miss.
-Thank you.
-I'm Damian, by the way.
-Camia.
-Camia. Camia.
[soft piano music continues]
[groaning]
[Damian] Camia, believe me. I've changed.
I'm not a criminal anymore.
I live a completely different life now.
[Camia] I'll give you a chance
to prove yourself.
[Damian] Is there anything
I can do to help?
Thank you for coming.
I'll do anything for you and Lily.
[soft piano music continues]
[Camia] Damian.
Forgive me for thinking badly of you.
If you love someone, you
need to express how you feel,
so you won't have any regrets.
[soft piano music continues]
I love you, Camia.
And I know you feel something for me too.
But why do you keep holding back?
Is it because of my past?
Is it because I don't deserve you?
I don't understand
my feelings for you, Damian.
I know I can't fall for you.
My life fell apart when Dante died,
and I don't think I can love again.
[soft piano music continues]
[music fades]
Camia.
Is something wrong?
I'm just worried about Lily.
[melancholic music playing]
They'll bust Red Dragon tonight.
Damian, I know my daughter is doing this
because she wants all of us
to live a peaceful life.
And I trust her.
I know she can take on her enemies.
And that all her sacrifices will pay off.
All of this will be worth it.
[suspenseful music playing]
Madam, they're here.
Mr. Han.
All 200 people that you've ordered…
…are already accounted for.
[Mr. Han] I'm impressed.
Master will be pleased to know
about this transaction,
especially now…
…that you're back in control.
Yes, we had a bit
of an infestation problem.
But now that we are pest-free,
all operations are back in control.
-I never doubted you.
-Thank you, Mr. Han.
Flattery is cheap.
But then, what I need is
what we've already discussed.
Oh, right. Okay.
Coming.
Agent Salonga, what are we waiting for?
We need to wait till Red Dragon
is holding the payment herself.
Don't worry. Our intel is
already there waiting to attack.
[suspenseful music playing]
That's all yours.
-[Mr. Han] Did you like it?
-[Helena chuckles]
-My besties.
-Oh, right.
[Helena] They're beautiful.
[Mr. Tan] I'm happy.
Are you happy too?
-Of course, I am.
-All right. Here you go.
[suspenseful music playing]
I knew it. You're a traitor!
[suspenseful music continues]
Hey. What is going on?
Madam, he's spying on us!
Diego!
-Agent Salonga.
-Let's go.
Men, move, move, move!
You bastard!
[suspenseful music playing]
Police! Don't move!
-[gunshots]
-[Red Dragon screams]
[gunshots resume]
Get up!
[suspenseful music playing]
Let's go.
Let's move.
What are you waiting for?
[suspenseful music continues]
Gotcha.
Caught you red-handed, Red Dragon.
Trying to escape again?
This time, I'll make sure
you won't get away.
[car door opens]
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you
in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney
and have him present with you
while you are being questioned.
If you can't afford one,
one will be appointed to represent you
for any questioning if you wish.
You can decide at any time
to exercise these rights
or not answer any questions
or make any statements.
[ominous music playing]
Don't celebrate yet, Lily Cruz.
This isn't over.
I won't let you get away with this!
-I'll make you pay!
-Empty threats, Red Dragon!
You're all talk!
You really are Emilia's mother.
You both think you breathe fire,
but all you blow is hot air!
And you, Diego Torillo!
You will pay for this treachery!
Mark my words!
You will both pay!
You will both burn in hell!
I will burn you two alive!
-[Red Dragon screams]
-[Lily laughs]
Aww. Go on, Agent Salonga.
How sad. The dragon is throwing a fit.
-Let's go.
-[grunts]
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues]
[breathes heavily]
-[screams]
-[glass breaks]
That Diego Torillo!
He made my mother look like a fool!
You! All of you! Get out! Get out!
[tense music playing]
Lily and Diego, this is the last straw.
But just remember
that Baby Dragon is
still here out to get you.
[tense music continues]
[soft piano music playing]
This is all new to me, Jepoy.
But I know and I'm sure
that you will never hurt me.
[soft piano music continues]
I'm ready, Jepoy.
I'll give you my all
because I love you too.
[soft piano music playing]
[knocking on door]
[unsettling music playing]
-Ouch.
-Hello, lover boy.
You know, you're--
Yes?
Where are my weapons?
What did you say?
I said where are my guns?
Oh!
You don't have to be so mad.
Give them back.
Like I said, Madrigal,
if you want it, come and get it.
-You're really pushing me.
-One, two…
[unsettling music continues]
Natalie.
Natalie!
I missed you, Madrigal.
I know she can't give you…
-…what you need.
-Stop it!
And you know that I can.
You remember, right?
Hmm?
I'm going to surprise Jepoy.
[tense music playing]
Natalie, stop.
Stop, Natalie! We've talked about this!
Stop resisting, Madrigal.
You know, you can trust me.
It can be our little secret.
I'm not gonna tell her.
And I know you won't.
It could be for old times' sake.
For the last time.
Promise.
[sensual music playing]
-Is this what you want?
-Mm-hm.
-Hmm?
-[giggles]
This? Is this what you want?
Mm-hm.
[sensual music continues]
[exhales]
Are you gonna punish me?
I'm going to hurt you.
[tense music playing]
You love Jepoy, Anna.
You don't have to be scared.
Jepoy would never hurt you
because he loves you.
[tense music continues]
[clicks]
[door creaks]
[tense music playing]
Jepoy.
Hi, Anna.
[breathes heavily]
Anna, it's not what you think.
Anna! Anna!
What have I done?
[tense music playing]
This is your fault!
-[squeals]
-This is all your fault!
Anna! Anna!
Anna, wait!
Poor, Madrigal.
He doesn't even know it yet,
but he's gonna be all mine.
[chuckles]
[sobbing]
You liar!
You're disgusting!
[sobbing]
Anna! Anna!
Anna, I'm sorry.
Anna, wait. Wait. Please forgive me.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Sorry.
Get your hands off me, you liar!
Anna.
-How could you do this to me?
-Please. I'm sorry.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to.
I didn't mean it.
Oh, really?
Sorry.
You didn't mean to lie
and hurt me, Jepoy?!
I'm such an idiot!
I was so stupid to think you
were different from other men!
But, it turns out you're worse!
[sobbing]
I didn't mean to, Anna.
I was weak. Please forgive me.
-Don't touch me!
-Please forgive me.
-Don't…
You're the only one I love, Anna.
No one else! Just you!
Just you, I swear!
I thought you'd never hurt me.
And we've been friends for so long!
We've always treated each
other like family, remember?
Jepoy, in every future
I dreamed of, you were in it!
I was ready to give you all of me!
But you threw it all away for that woman!
Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry, Anna. Sorry. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
-Jepoy.
-Sorry, Anna. Please.
I'm sorry.
Anna, please forgive me.
If it's Natalie you want,
then just go with her.
No. You're the one I want, Anna.
You two disgust me.
No, Anna.
Anna.
Please, Anna!
[solemn music playing]
[exhales]
[sobs]
[sniffles and sobs]
Open the door, please.
Montoya! You have a visitor.
[unsettling music playing]
[lock opens]
[unsettling music continues]
Mama.
-Mama, how are you?
-I'm good.
[sighs]
Mama, I hope you're not
blaming me for what happened.
Emilia.
I trusted you with this transaction.
Do you realize how much money
we lost because we failed?
But I did everything I could, Mama.
Then explain to me how we got caught!
It's Lily Cruz, Mama.
She doesn't know how to give up.
You know, ever since
she started investigating you,
all the way until you went
to Macau and back,
she's been acting like a superhero.
And now, she thinks she's a special agent.
If you have connections in
law enforcement, she does too.
She doesn't want to give up!
And that Diego Torillo, Mama.
That bastard!
You know, you never heard from me,
Mama, because I trusted you!
Because I thought you had a plan
to use him against Lily Cruz!
Well, I did have a plan!
Yes, but what happened?
Lily Cruz got to you first.
She defeated us.
We just lost to her again,
and I won't stand for it, Mama!
I won't let this slide.
I'm going to get you out of here,
and we're going to make her pay.
Don't make promises, Emilia. Fulfill them.
And this time, you better not fail.
Okay, Mama.
I'll be needing every cent
from your piggy bank.
I'll be using that to crush Lily Cruz.
But the problem is, Mama,
you're left with nothing.
Your account is frozen.
Your properties and assets are gone.
Technically speaking,
you have nothing, Mama.
Zero.
That is where you're wrong, Emilia.
What do you mean, Mama?
Do you have some hidden money?
Yes, I do have my hidden wealth.
[tense music playing]
Helena Montoya's reputation is ruined.
But, Diego, that's not enough.
I want her to lose her power.
And for that to happen,
she needs to lose all her money.
I'm sure she's still got
a secret stash of money.
You're right.
I discovered another one
of Helena Montoya's secrets.
And once we expose it,
she'll lose her power for sure.
[tense music playing]
[Diego] I saw them loading
sacks of cash into a vehicle.
So, I followed them.
Romulo, do you have the money Madam sent?
It's all here.
Go ahead and unload it.
Hurry.
[tense music playing]
Let's go.
[Diego] So, if Red Dragon is hiding money,
I know where we can find it.
But the area is loaded
with CCTV cameras and guards.
The whole place is built like Fort Knox.
And if security is that tight,
I don't think it's just loose change
she's got stacked in there.
Now, Red Dragon isn't
just planning her escape.
She's figuring out a way
to protect her hidden wealth.
[Emilia] I knew it.
Someone like you has deep pockets.
No one else knows about this
except for Romulo.
Now, he's in prison.
That means you're the only person
I can trust, Emilia.
So now, you have to act fast.
Secure my money as soon as possible.
[tense music playing]
Thanks, Mama.
Thank you, Mama, for trusting me again.
I will not fail you.
And I assure you, Emilia,
no matter how many times
Lily Cruz tries to bring us down,
as long as we have money,
we have power.
The one and only Red Dragon
will rise again and again.
[tense music continues]
[Lily] Here's what we'll do, Diego.
We need to make sure we get
our hands on Helena's money
before she does.
That's what we need to do,
so we can make sure
that woman loses everything she has.
I'll see you at the
finish line, Red Dragon,
and may the best woman win.
[Camia] Lily.
-I'm glad you're both safe.
-Yes, Mom.
-Diego.
-Auntie.
[somber music playing]
Red Dragon and her lackeys
have been caught.
That's great. All thanks to you two.
This isn't the end.
A dragon doesn't just stop breathing fire.
Though I hope you still accept me
when you find out who I really am.
[somber music continues]
[reporter] Authorities nabbed
international syndicate
leader, Red Dragon,
in an entrapment
operation conducted by the NBI
through the help of famed
businesswoman, Lily Cruz.
This is what I'm talking about.
That is why I will never send
a woman to do a man's job.
Bet your bottom dollar
that women will just mess up everything.
What's the biggest mistake
of that syndicate?
They allowed a woman to be their leader.
[reporter] According to reports,
Diego Torillo played a huge part
in Red Dragon's arrest
by infiltrating the group
as a double agent.
There's another one.
I am starting to have a new-found respect
for that bastard half-brother of yours.
You know why?
Number one.
He ended up killing Colonel Sanggano.
And that is a feat by itself already.
Second…
Who would have thought
he'd drive your grandmother into a corner?
[laughs]
-Wait, I'm sorry.
-What's so funny?
No, no, no. I'm sorry.
Well…
This is just my opinion.
Diego only manages to score now because…
I'm watching from the sidelines.
But now that I'm back…
I'll put him in his rightful place.
My baby brother.
You know you're getting
scarier as the days go by.
You're becoming more cunning.
You're becoming slyer than I am.
[chuckles]
Now I can truly say…
that you don't have dragon blood in you.
The only thing running through your veins…
is pure, unadulterated Ardiente blood.
-[exhales]
-That's what makes you run.
[sighs]
[clears throat]
Grandpa.
Bless you. Bless you.
[chuckles]
I am blessed!
I'm just so blessed because I was given…
-a grandson like you!
-Oh, come on.
-Cheers.
-Viva, Ardiente!
[laughs maniacally]
[line rings]
[intercept tone]
Anna, why aren't you picking up?
[line rings]
-[intercept tone]
-You too, Jepoy.
It's late.
I've been trying to reach Anna and Jepoy,
but they won't pick up.
You're worrying about
your friends too much.
Diego, you know me.
I can't help but worry
about the people I love,
and by that, I mean all of you.
Like how I worry about you?
Diego.
What?
[romantic music playing]
I'm ready to give up my life for you.
I know that. You've proven
that so many times now.
For that, I'm thankful because
you're back by my side.
[romantic music continues]
Because we're soulmates.
[romantic music playing]
I was so lost.
I ended up killing someone.
But you didn't give up on me.
You pulled me from the edge.
Thank you.
I'll always be here for you, Diego.
No matter what happens…
I'll always be by your side.
We'll always be together.
And I don't want to lose you again.
That won't happen again.
I promise you…
that you'll never lose me.
[romantic music playing]
We've been through a lot lately.
So now, let's make things easier.
I know we're in
the middle of a war, Diego.
But I think it's worth the fight
when you aren't alone.
Diego.
From now on…
let's make it official.
Will you be mine?
[romantic music playing]
[chuckles lightly]
Well?
Yes.
-I'm all yours.
-[chuckles]
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" playing]
[breathes heavily]
[song fades]
[tense music playing]
[Diego] That's the area.
That's where I followed Romulo.
[Diego] I'm sure that's where
he brought Red Dragon's money.
There are lots of guards
and security cameras.
[Lily] It's like a fortress
you can't penetrate.
I wonder how vast Red Dragon's fortune is,
for her to protect it like that.
No one knows.
But Red Dragon really wants
to keep her wealth secure.
There are high walls surrounding it.
I don't care how high those walls are.
I can tear anything down.
[tense music continues]
That Diego's a bastard.
I told her from the start
that you can't trust that man!
I'm going to kill him
once I get out of here.
Chill, Romulo. Chill. Come on, calm down.
I know we both want Diego dead.
But first things first,
you need to tell me everything
you know about Mama's riches.
Because as of now, you and I
are the only people that Mama trusts.
That's why you need to tell me everything.
We need to work together,
so we can recover Mama's entire fortune.
[tense music playing]
[ominous music playing]
How can she make a comeback
when she's dirt-poor?!
[Emilia] What the police have is
only the tip of the iceberg.
[Lily] I don't care how high
those walls are.
[Julio] You and I have a
common enemy-- Lily Cruz.
What if I can tell you
that I can offer you
that alliance against Lily Cruz,
and, most importantly,
that I can guarantee your freedom?
[theme music playing]